Not even making the Major.
连 Major 都没打进。
Everything was going against them.
几乎所有事都对他们不利。
They were down and beaten.
他们一度被打得很惨，士气也很低。
But they showed up to Fort Worth with vigor,
但他们来到 Fort Worth 时，
and looking to try to make it all the way
依然带着一股冲劲，
to the grand finals.
想一路冲进总决赛。
And we'll see if they can get it done with that.
看看他们能不能真的做到。
I think the players are just about ready.
我想选手们已经差不多准备好了。
It's going to be a feast to watch for us.
这场比赛对我们来说绝对是一场盛宴。
Na'Vi, the second-best team in the world,
Na'Vi，世界排名第二的队伍，
they want that bout versus Vitality.
他们想拿到和 Vitality 交手的机会。
But FaZe, they are ready.
但 FaZe 也已经准备好了。
They're ready to fight down in the dirt,
他们已经准备好去打这种硬仗、
here in Fort Worth.
就在 Fort Worth 这片赛场上。
On this stage today,
今天站在这个舞台上的，
we have two of the most storied organizations
是两支 Counter-Strike 历史上
in Counter-Strike history.
最有传奇色彩的俱乐部。
On one side, FaZe, led by Twistzz,
一边是 FaZe，由 Twistzz 领衔，
North America's most decorated ever player,
他也是北美荣誉最多的选手之一。
And his challenge today
而他今天面对的挑战，
is to call against
就是要和另一位指挥正面对抗，
a Major-winning veteran in-game leader
那是一位拿过 Major 的老牌指挥，
in Aleksib. The odds are stacked against FaZe Clan,
也就是 Aleksib。现在外界普遍不看好 FaZe Clan，
but they have been every single step of the way.
但这一路走来，他们始终都是在这种处境里打出来的。
We have been coming to this great state
我们来到这片伟大的土地，
for over two decades.
已经超过二十年了。
Counter-Strike lives and breathes in Texas.
Counter-Strike 在德州是真正有生命力、有呼吸感的。
So Fort Worth,
所以，Fort Worth，
let us hear why Counter-Strike comes to Texas.
让我们听听，为什么 Counter-Strike 会属于德州。
And the semi-finals are live.
半决赛正式开打。
Dust2.
地图是 Dust2。
And we've already got a little bit of aggression
开局我们就已经看到一点主动性了，
up middle.
来自中路方向。
Na'Vi's gonna be starting on the CT side
Na'Vi 这边先做 CT，
as they attempt to quell
他们要想办法压住
this incredible push from FaZe into these playoffs.
FaZe 这次季后赛阶段非常猛的冲势。
Out towards long and they're not slowing down.
FaZe 往长 A 出，完全没有减速。
They're coming in quick.
他们冲得很快。
Long is already smoked, the cross is already up.
长 A 的烟已经给上，过点烟也已经铺好了。
Aleksib and iM playing in behind it.
Aleksib 和 iM 藏在烟后面防守。
broky throwing support utility,
broky 这边在给辅助道具，
shuffling in.
队友继续往里贴。
And no one providing resistance just yet,
目前还没人能第一时间顶住，
but now they've found themselves in the A bomb site.
FaZe 已经顺利进到了 A 包点。
All over the site, bomb plant gonna be coming through.
A 点已经被他们全面占住，雷也马上要下上。
w0nderful's slipped away back into CT spawn, and
w0nderful 已经退回 CT 出口，
iM is just gonna wait on down towards CT,
iM 也在 CT 一带等队友会合，
so because they're setting up for the retake utility,
因为 Na'Vi 这边是在布置回防道具，
it's not gonna go in towards the site.
所以这些道具不会直接丢进包点里。
Time to start this retake.
现在该正式开始回防了。
For Na'Vi, they're gonna find the first kill.
Na'Vi 这边先拿到回防的第一枪。
Cat side, they move in.
他们从 A 小方向一起压进来。
It's gonna be traded.
但立刻就被换掉了。
Still finally entering the kill feed here for Na'Vi,
Na'Vi 总算开始在击杀列表里有所回应，
but the kit goes down
但拆包钳掉在了地上，
towards CT, and it's all
位置就在 CT 方向，局面一下子又
over again, but FaZe bite back.
重新偏向了 FaZe。
Headshot delivered.
一发爆头打出来。
Now they're looking for more.
现在还在继续找后续击杀。
Sit back down.
给你按回去。
Exactly what FaZe needed is the hot start,
这正是 FaZe 最需要的那种强势开局，
and again, you get this kid,
而且你又看到了这个年轻人，
and coming into this lineup,
加入这套阵容之后，
how impressive has he been, delivering important kills,
他已经打出了太多关键人头，
big clutches for FaZe through this run.
也在这段征程里替 FaZe 拿下了不少关键残局。
Adds another big pistol-round clutch.
现在他又补上了一个关键的手枪局残局。
And a team with this new lineup,
而这支新阵容的队伍，
Launders spoke about it coming together.
Launders 之前就说过，他们正在越打越成型。
We saw yesterday, love playing with momentum,
我们昨天也看到了，他们特别擅长借势往前打，
it's a great strength of theirs,
这本来就是他们的一大强项，
and you've got to start on a positive note.
而今天他们也确实是以一个很好的开局起势了。
Great to see the pistol here
能拿下这个手枪局当然很好，
for FaZe, but the issue is
对 FaZe 来说问题在于，
they've still got to go with another buy.
他们下一回合还是得再补一轮枪。